Guide to the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
5488 B
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
669 linear feet.
Correspondence, Rule books, Agreements, etc.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
SUBJECTS
Names:
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
Subjects:
Railroads--Employees--Labor unions--United States--Sources.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted. Please contact the Kheel Center Reference Archivist for access information.
COLLECTION ARRANGEMENT
This forms a portion of collection #5488 B. The guide to the entire collection is available here.
Series XXV is arranged in 1 sub-series by Union file number.
Series XXVI is arranged in 11 sub-series by Union file number.
CONTAINER LIST
- Series XXV. RAILWAY CLERK
  - Sub-Series 236-0. Railway Clerk
    - General ("See Special File for Correspondence re President's Page."), 1964-1965 (Box 157, Folder 44)
      January 1, 1964-December 31, 1965.
    - General, 1963 (Box 157, Folder 45)
      January 1, 1963-December 31, 1963.
    - General, 1938-1962 (Box 157, Folder 46)
      1938-December 31, 1962.
- Series XXVI. DISCIPLINE
  - Sub-Series 237-212. Discipline
    - Andrew A. Nyby, Lodge No. 630, Pacific Lodge, Vancouver, British Columbia, Canada, 1950 (Box 158, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Series 237-164. Discipline
    - Robert Bayer, Joseph Hanna, Thos. Tyrell, Lodge No. 2125, 1944-1959 (Box 157, Folder 47)
  - Sub-Series 237-179. Discipline
    - Clarence B. Carter, Lodge No. 227, Elm City Lodge, New Haven, Connecticut, 1948-1949 (Box 158, Folder 1)
  - Sub-Series 237-216. Discipline
    - J.T. Donohue, Lodge No. 2215, Jersey City, New Jersey, 1949-1958 (Box 157, Folder 48)
  - Sub-Series 237-244. Discipline
    - W.T. Harrison, Lodge No. 178, Louisville, Kentucky, 1954 (Box 158, Folder 3)
    - W.T. Harrison, Lodge No. 178, Louisville, Kentucky, 1953 (Box 158, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 237-245. Discipline
    - Marvin F. Rice, Lodge No. 2063, Jacksonville, Florida, 1951 (Box 158, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 237-269. Discipline
    - Almeta Hunter, Lodge No. 124, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1956-1958 (Box 157, Folder 50)
  - Sub-Series 237-270. Discipline
    - Moses Ruffin, Lodge No. 124, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1956-1958 (Box 157, Folder 51)
  - Sub-Series 237-272. Discipline
    - Morris A. Bracey, Lodge No. 124, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1956-1958 (Box 157, Folder 52)
  - Sub-Series 237-273. Discipline
    - William Mullane, Lodge No. 124, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1956-1958 (Box 157, Folder 53)
  - Sub-Series 237-276. Discipline
    - Edgie Wallace, Lodge No. 124, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1956-1958 (Box 157, Folder 49)
    - Edgie Wallace, Lodge No. 124, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1957 (Box 158, Folder 6)